Hello Namaskar friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel Investment Information
[Music]
Company. Friends, this insurance company does
insurance.
Friends, on the very first day the market opened today,
it was at
Rs. 1209. You will
know that there are a few
people who are selling. Most of the
people have bought, in which
73 percent of the people are
selling, and about 25% of the people are selling.
So this stock has maintained a lot of
momentum
and talking about holding, we will keep
giving updates on the best stocks. If you liked the video, then
like and share the video. And if
you have not opened a demand account yet, then
its link is given in the description of the video.
You
can go there and open your demand account and
go on your journey, that is, you
can accumulate your money, which is reducing your money.
As you can see, the
market is going very well even now.
What this company does is insurance,
like there is insurance for mobile people
and there are products also.
Some are fridge insurance, some are insurance,
so this company is insurance.  Insurance etc.